supercircuits.com 2012-11-08

# Support - FAQs - Policies - Product Resources

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.supercircuits.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site.

#### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

All personally identifying information collected through www.supercircuits.com is for Supercircuits staff to process and manage subscriptions, track site usage patterns and statistics, or to deliver services through the site. Such information may also be used by us for market research or for prize or information-request fulfillment unless otherwise indicated.

Such information will not be posted or published by us, and, except as specified below in this privacy policy regarding anonymous aggregated data, or to provide services to you on behalf of Supercircuits, it will not be provided to third-party providers without consent.

If you choose to provide personally identifying information to us, you may receive the following types of e-mails from us:

  * E-mails related to subscription-maintenance activities.
  * Periodic e-mail newsletters highlighting new features, content, and usage tips for www.supercircuits.com.
  * Periodic special offers for additional Supercircuits products and services.
  * Periodic special offers from Supercircuits approved partners if you opt-in or give us your permission to send them.

When you provide personally identifying information to us, you can let us know that you do not wish to receive special Supercircuits or partner offers. Each offer will also have information available to allow you to opt out if you wish to receive no further offers.

You may also opt out of any future contacts from us at any time by contacting us at 877-995-2288 or via our [contact form](http://www.supercircuits.com/contact.aspx).

#### Cookies

We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

#### Orders

We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your order.

#### Registration

In order to use advanced features of this website (such as viewing order history), a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as email address). This information may be used to contact you about the products on our site in which you have expressed interest.

#### Security

We take every precaution to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data or your account information), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.

We also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

 **If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us at 877-995-2288 or via our[contact form](http://www.supercircuits.com/contact.aspx).**
